# **Dhanesh Kumar**

Computer science student possessing the analytical abilities necessary for designing and developing mobile and web applications. Gained exposure to key concepts in react, MySQL, and data structures. Hand on experience of programming languages include JavaScript, Dart, C, C++, and python.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **Accenture**, Remote — Developer Program

Feb 2022 - Feb 2022

Contribution in debugging algorithm, design changing to an existing architecture, and applied Unit testing on smallest testable parts of an application

## Comfy Living, Remote — Amazon, and eBay store Manager

Oct 2020 - Dec 2020

A USA based furniture company having store on both amazon and eBay. Virtual responsibilities order management processing and updating store

## **Fiverr**, Remote — Freelancing

Jun 2019 - Present

worked on more than 20 projects in databases, data analysis and data preprocessing – Java, MySQL, regression, python.

## **EDUCATION**

## **NUST**, Islamabad — Bachelor

Sep 2018 - Present

## **Sindh Public College**, Umerkot — *Pre* - *Engineering*

Feb 2016 - Mar 2018

## **PROJECTS**

## **iTour (FYP)** — Flutter, Firebase, PyTorch

- A cross platform mobile app platform to plan a fully customized trip of an area based on your interests and preferences.
- The platform enables users to plan visiting sights and book nearby hotels.

## **Shopit** — JavaScript, HTML, CSS, and MySQL

- Designed and implemented the idea of distributed E-commerce marketplace
- Localize the e-commerce sales within a locality to enable quick delivery times and high availability at ease.

#### **Manaj** — Java, and MySQL

 Manages employee's salaries, deductions, other conveyance, net pay, bonuses, and generation of pay-slips

- Islamabad, Pakistan
- **03473377700**
- dmeghwar.bscs18seecs@seecs.edu.pk
- https://dhaneshkumar.me/
- in www.linkedin.com/in/dhaneshkumar20/

#### **SKILLS**

React, JavaScript

C, C++, java, python

Data structures and algorithm

#### **Position Responsibilities**

Member Team Admin Events at 15th HONET- ICT international conference.

**External relation** at NUST community service club

**Deputy Director Marketing** at SGA (Student Government Association)

#### **Achievements**

**Excellence performance award** by united helping hand foundation (UNIHHFO).

**Certification of Completion** in software engineering by Forage

#### **Professional Interest**

Mobile Application
Web Application
Competitive programming

#### **Hobbies**

Esports Cricket TV shows